Yes! See you tomorrow, Kirimaldo!
I'll make you crazy!
This is Yukirinuko and KashikomariYuki!
Chat!
Do you have a theory that I'm getting a taste for chit-chat?
Yes!
YouTube is just right for that.
I mean, it's not enough to talk on TV.
And when you don't have enough to talk about on TV, and you don't have enough to ask your friends to listen to you.
YouTube is just right for that.
I'd like to chat with you.
Today, my hair...I've been into this haircut lately.
But today, my hair and make-up artist decided to do it this way.
She decided on it for me.
It's kind of like... the outfit of a girl who wants to be a good girl.
You know what I mean?
I'm wearing a black fitted photo.
I'm wearing a lab and denim, but I'm not wearing this.
This menu is so big!
I, uh, I've never done this before.
I bought the place after we were able to shoot it. It's been a long time.
It rocks so much and it's great!
My birthday is coming up today, so I got a present!
First of all, this is awesome!
I have it!
The staff who took care of me during my French kiss, solo, and ABEX days, and the person who was in charge of the site this time, gave me this gift every year.
The one who was in charge of this event and the one who was in charge of this tour, both of them give me gifts every year. Last year it was a chou chou from Viton.
Before that, it was a shoulder bag from Valenshaga.
A purse! Isn't it so cute? It fits me so well right now. I'm going to use it. It's so cute!
Another gift from a hair and make-up artist that I've been working with today.
Isn't it amazing the way she has it? This is a bangs clip by Mitriz.
I told her how funny and kind she was the first time I worked with her, and to my surprise, she came back with a clip for my bangs!
So cute! Thank you very much. It was a present I received today.
I have a few things I want to talk to you about. A few things. Recently, a talk? I've had a lot of online conversations recently with fans in China and overseas who use a translation app.
Many of them use the app that translates the message in advance, and then when you say "Pon", they reply with a voice like "Yukirin, thank you so much for everything".
A Chinese fan, a guy about the same age as me, used the app to tap on someone like Yukirin, and he played it twice first.A Chinese fan, a guy about my age, pon the translation app to be like Yukirin, and he played it twice first.
The first one was that Yukirin is a cool young man. What? Like, "What? One more time, and still more. Then I said, "Pon.
Yukirin should surround herself with handsome young men. Isn't that so funny?
She's already 32, right? So I was told I should surround myself with young, good-looking guys in their early 20s.
How do your Chinese fans look at you? My Chinese fans. Not funny? I'm not into that kind of thing. I'm not.
I had only 6 or 10 seconds to go before I had to leave. I was laughing when I was told that I only had about 6 seconds left to go.
I was on the edge of my seat, and I said, "I've got money left.
And then, "bang!
I just said it in a moment. It wasn't like that, but I said it.
Also, this is really not a big story. I was walking home from the station the other day.
There was a boy sitting on the street, about the age of a kindergarten student.
And he was really sulking. I was worried about him.
But you'd be scared if a 32-year-old suddenly approached you like this, wouldn't you? So I thought, "I'm worried about him.
He stood there, found some rocks, and was kicking them and sulking a bit more.
You know what I mean? He was kind of toddling around. Did something happen?
I, the boy, and the parent and child in front of them. They were holding hands.
And this girl was about the same age as this boy, in kindergarten.
This girl kept looking at the boy behind her and saying something like, "What's going on?
But the mother can't see them. Do you understand? She's like, "I'm coming.
But she doesn't know what he's doing. So, so that the mother doesn't know, the girl keeps looking at the boy and saying something like...
Like, "Oh, she's doing great! That's so nice! I thought.
If I had a child, I would want her to grow up to be a girl like that.
Then, the boy sat down again. The girl was worried, and was looking for a stone that was probably missing.
I could see it, but I was afraid that the woman, who I didn't know, would pull out the rock.
So I thought, "I have it! I thought, "I have it," but as I was doing this, the stone hit me right here with a bang. I thought it was the same one.
I thought it was the same one. I thought, "I gave it back to him.
The moment I passed by, the boy found the stone and hit it with a bang! and hit me right here.
That was the worst.
I felt really sad. I felt funny and sad.
I'd like to tell you about it someday, maybe in a few years, but it's kind of a big deal these days.
I don't know what to say about it.
I don't know what to say. It's super shocking. It's not my fault, but....
It was an incident that taught me not to let my guard down in life. It wasn't really an incident. It was solved. It was solved.
I never thought I would be caught up in something like this.
I want to tell you, but I can't. But I want to tell you someday.
I want to alert people.I want to give you a heads up.
I was already feeling a little down about it, and yesterday, in the middle of the shoot, that was resolved.
Then the staff told me that my expression in the photos had obviously brightened up.
I was so depressed that it affected the photo shoot.
I was pretty depressed. But it was resolved. I'm glad.
And lastly, a super unimportant story. Apps and recently some apps with points and stuff.
Matsukiyo? I go to Matsukidai's once in a while, so I have the points app installed.
Then, when I was buying at the cash register, the clerk asked me if I had played Matsukidai Roulette today. I was told, "Did you play Matsukiyo Roulette today?
What is Matsukiyo Roulette? I thought, "What is Matsukiyo Roulette?
I looked at the app and saw that Tokai On Air was running a campaign.
When I opened the app, I was told to go to the Tokai On Air section.
So I played it while the cashier was selling the tickets.
Then I could do it twice, twice a day.
There are three prizes, A, B, and C. Prize A and C are discount coupons.
The A and C prizes are like discount coupons, and the B prize is for goodies.
I thought it was great that I could do it twice. It doesn't fall off. I'm not talking about this at all.
And I thought it was great because I could do it twice. And it's so kind.
Did you do it today? I asked him if he had done it today, and he gave me a discount.
I did it this way and this way, and both times I missed out.
I thought, "What? I thought to myself.
I thought, "Is it that easy to get a discount?
I thought, "Ah," and just left it at that.
Then he said, "Did you do it? I was told, "Did you do it?
I said, "Yes, I did. I said, "Yes, I did.
And he asked me, "What did you hit? He said, "What did you win?
Oh, what? Neither one of them was a hit. It didn't work.
You missed both times? I was told.
So maybe.
I had a good chance of winning one or the other,
I happened to be recommended by the staff to try it,
I was recommended by the staff, but I lost both times, and the atmosphere was really awkward.
It was amazing.
I was so embarrassed.
I haven't had any luck lately.
It's not my lucky day.
Hmmm.Hmmm.
No sasai on it?
No sasai on it.
I don't mind it, but when it overlaps with something else,
This one might not work either. Like this one too.
I know, right?
But I was a little lucky.
It's really a small happiness.
You know, the drink fridge was room temperature.
When it was cold.
I wanted to drink Calpis with it,
I put it in the freezer and forgot all about it,
I thought it was absolutely frozen,
I thought it was absolutely frozen, but it turned into a sorbet just like that,
That's the happiest thing I've had recently.
It's tiny.
Tiny.
This candy was delicious.
Some kind of sea urchin-flavored potato sticks,
and black truffle potato chips.
They were really tasty.
But I'm holding back a lot of sweets.
It was delicious.
I guess that's about it.
So, I've talked a little bit about my recent life,
I'm going to be 32 years old from now on,
I wish for good things to happen. I really do.
I've decided that I'm going to improve my daily conduct.
I decided to do it.
I've got eyes.
You said it's okay to have eyes.
Is that so?
I got a bad one,
I let it out.
Huh. I let it out.
Well, that's the end of the shooting.Come on, so the shooting is over.
But you wound up. The shooting.
That's good.
Eh, no. It's on.
I'm sorry. It's on.
That's solid.
But a little bit.
It's a bit curly.
It's nice to be able to go home while it's still light.
So I'm going to be careful on my way home.
Please listen to my ramblings again.
That's all for now.
Thank you for watching.